Summary

Innovative and energetic Senior UX Designer and Senior Graphic Designer with over 15 years of experience creating exceptional visual designs and user-friendly experiences. Managing multiple projects simultaneously and meeting tight deadlines. Excellent communication skills and interpersonal skills, building positive relationships with internal and external customers.

Experience

BenefitHub - UX Designer II

Tampa, FL - July 2015 - October 2024

- Created mockups for BenefitHub's employee discount and perks platform to promote a great user experience
- Designed landing pages, web apps, modules, widgets, content pages and more for ultimate user engagement
- Generated interactive prototypes in Adobe XD to showcase design and functionality for internal approvals
- Incorporated data-driven elements in mockups to accurately display various components of the platform
- Developed responsive, mobile-first products using HTML5, CSS3, SASS and JavaScript to satisfy requirements
- Collaborated with team members using email, Slack, Jira, Teams and Zoom for effective communication
- Partnered with front-end and back-end developers for precision and on-time deliverables
- Inspected development projects with cross-browser testing across multiple devices for utmost accuracy
- Complied with WCAG web accessibility standards to ensure designs maintained optimal compatibility
- Built Adobe libraries to replicate our UI Kit Design System of React.js components such as buttons, modals, input fields, navigation, as well as style libraries for fonts, color themes, etc. to promote design consistency

Raymond James Financial - Web Admin Contractor

St. Petersburg, FL - February 2015 - June 2015

- Constructed websites with Sitecore CMS, HTML and CSS producing high conversion rates for financial officers
- Designed logos, graphics and web banners resulting in creative brand consistency throughout the site
- Edited, cropped and optimized photos using best practices increasing speed of delivery

Sign-Age - Senior Graphic Designer and Web Assistant

Clearwater, FL - August 2011 - June 2014

- Updated the company website content and images using Firespring CMS to increase client engagement
- Designed various signs, banners, etc. for retail, POP, indoor and outdoor architectural signs, trade shows, vehicle wraps, wall murals and more, while adhering to ADA standards and achieving high customer satisfaction
- Prepared art files for wide-format printing and outsourcing to vendors resulting in ultimate print quality
- Produced 3D-sign technical drawings that assured city, county, and contract approvals needed for construction

Tampa Print Services (now AlphaGraphics) - **Pre-Press Manager and Sr. Graphic Designer** Tampa, FL - April 2003 - March 2011

- Managed the pre-press dept., ensuring the press and digital depts. produced maximum quality products
- Handled design, pre-press and software updates to stay on schedule and ensure deadlines were met
- Designed logos, brochures, corporate identity packages, B2B materials, etc. to promote various businesses
- Prepared art files for offset, flexo, wide-format and digital printing for optimized printed materials

Freelance & Contract Work - Graphic Designer and UX Designer/Developer

St. Petersburg, FL - January 2010 - Present

- Create, update and develop landing pages and websites to advance online presence for various businesses
- Design logos, brochures, package designs, social media ads, marketing materials, etc. to boost customer brands
- Enhance imagery and optimize photos for print and web to gain excitement of products and attract end users
- Produce motion graphic videos, music lyric videos and social media pieces to boost sales and engagement

Education

St. Petersburg College

St. Petersburg, FL

Associate of Science - Computer Science, Web Development

Coding Dojo Web Development Boot Camp

Mountain View, CA

Three-month web development training course

Academy of Creative Arts College of Design

Cincinnati, OH

Associate of Arts - Commercial Art

Software

Adobe Creative Cloud | Adobe XD | Adobe Illustrator | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe InDesign | Adobe Audition Adobe After Effects | Adobe Acrobat | Adobe Dreamweaver | Microsoft Office Suite | Google Suite | Visual Studio Visual Studio Code | Figma | Miro | Visio | Sitecore CMS | Firespring CMS | WordPress | Wix |

Skills & Tools

UI/UX Design | Graphic Design | Front-End Development | Mobile-First Development | HTML5 | CSS3 | SASS JavaScript | jQuery | React.js | JSON | Media Queries | GitHub | Azure DevOps | Jira | Monday | Zoom | Slack Teams | Cross-Browser Testing | Copywriting | Dieline Drawing | Technical Drawing | Technical Writing | Editing ADA Compliance | WCAG Web Accessibility | Scrum | Agile | Design Systems